> > 布莱恩: 让我们去使用 Dropdown.
&gt;&gt; Brian: Let's go to useDropdown.
所以我们要重命名 useDropdown.js
So we're gonna rename useDropdown.js,
重命名为点 tsx。
rename that to be dot tsx.
它认为它很开心现在很不安
It thinks it's happy, now it's upset.
好的好的
Okay, great.
>> Brian: 因此，我们需要更新或获取更多内容。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So we need to update or
get a couple more things from this.
我们需要此操作来导入设置状态操作和分派。
We need this to import set
state action and dispatch.
>> 布莱恩: 好吧，标签是什么 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, what is label?
标签是 a， >> Brian: String。
Label is a,
&gt;&gt; Brian: String.
我在注释中粘贴了错误的内容， >> Brian: DefaultState
I pasted the wrong thing in my notes so,
&gt;&gt; Brian: DefaultState
将会是任何一个
is going to be an any.
>> Brian: 选项将成为一系列字符串。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
options is going to be a array of strings.
>> Brian: 因此，下拉内容本身就是一个功能组件。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So drop down in and
of itself is a function component.
>> 布莱恩: 这样也可以从 React 中获取。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
it will grab that from React as well.
>> 布莱恩: 那么，它是否知道 updateState ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then,
does it know updateState is?
是啊这就是调度和下拉的状态
Yeah, that's a dispatch and
dropdown, and state.
所以我们甚至可以说， >> 布莱恩: 让我们看看，国家。
So we could even go as far and say,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Let's see, state.
>> Brian: 状态。
&gt;&gt; Brian: State.
> > Brian: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Yeah.
> > 布莱恩: 那么在这个情况下，我们不知道什么是什么国家，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So in this case, we don't
actually know what states gonna be,
我们真的做到了不是吗
actually we do, don't we?
状态始终是字符串。
State is always going to be a string.
>> 布莱恩: 这是真的。
&gt;&gt; Brian: That's true.
所以请将此字符串作为字符串。
So make this a string.
> > 布莱恩: 因为你在处理一个选择，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Because you're
dealing with a select, right?
而这一选择总是要处理字符串。
And that select is always going
to be dealing with strings.
所以你可以强迫每个人给你个条件
So you can just go ahead and
force everyone to give you strings.
> > 布莱恩: 好吧，然后我估计我们不需要这些了，所以
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, and then I guess we
didn't actually need these ones, so
你可以把这些都删除
you can go ahead and delete those.
SetStateAction 和 Dispatch， okay.
SetStateAction and Dispatch, okay.
> > 布莱恩: 酷，关于 useDropdown的任何问题 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Cool,
any questions about useDropdown?
这很直接
It was pretty straightforward.
你只需要确定参数，其他的东西就会发生。
You just have to identify the parameters
and everything else kinda fell into place.
然后我们只需要一点点的精练来确定
And then, we just kind of refined
useDropdown a little bit to make sure this
绝对是函数组件，而不仅仅是通用 JSX。
is definitely a function component and
not just generic JSX.
你真的要区分这一点，但也可能是这样。
Nothing you've really have to distinguish
that very often, but might as well.
> > 布莱恩: 我现在还有 10 分钟，还有 8 分钟的时间，好吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: I got like ten more minutes now,
eight more minutes to finish it, okay?
> > 布莱恩: 现在我们去完成搜索程序
&gt;&gt; Brian: So
let's go finish search params now.
>> Brian: 我们重命名为 .tsx。
&gt;&gt; Brian: We renamed that to .tsx.
我们需要知道这是一个 FunctionComponent ，我们去拿吧。
We need to tell that this is a
FunctionComponent, so let's go grab that.
结果可能会很沮丧，因为我们还没有确定结果。
Results can be upset at,
because we haven't defined results yet.
而且我们也要进口
And we're also need to get import
路由器的 RouteCmponentProps 。
RouteCmponentProps from reach/Router.
好的我们会在上面移动的
Okay, we'll move that up there.
> > 布莱恩: 然后，我们还需要主人/宠物的动物。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And then,
we also need animal from the master/pet.
像那样的动物
So animal, like that.
所以搜索参数是一个功能组件。
So search params is a function component.
> > 布莱恩: 它的组件，一个路线组件道具，
&gt;&gt; Brian: And it takes its components,
a route component props,
它本身不期望任何类型的标识或来自 Reach 路由器的任何内容。
It itself is not expecting any sort of
ID or anything coming from Reach Router.
它的 URL 中没有任何通配符或变量。
It doesn't have any wildcards or
variables in its URL.
所以我们不需要给出任何参数
So we don't have to give this
one any sort of parameters,
而我们以前做过对吧
whereas we did before, right?
> > 布莱恩: 那我们要做的就是
&gt;&gt; Brian: Then,
the one that we have to do here is
useDropdown， "Animal"， ANIMALS。
useDropdown, "Animal", ANIMALS.
我想找的就是 > > 布莱恩: 这是
The one that I'm looking for is,
&gt;&gt; Brian: This is
另一个就是宠物变成永远的地方对吧
another one of this where
the pets becomes a never, right?
它为我们提供了一个阵列，但它不让我们触摸它，所以你必须在这里说。
It gives us an array but it won't let us
touch it, so you have to tell it here.
这是一个阵列，但最终将会是一个动物的阵列。
This is an array, but this is eventually
going to be an array of animal,
从空气污染指数中恢复过来的
that are coming back from the API.
> > 布莱恩: 和品种一样。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And same with thing with breeds.
这将作为字符串数组。
This is going to be as string array.
>> Brian: 类型，位置字符串，品种字符串或分派，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Type, location string,
breed string, or dispatch, right?
这就是我们需要改变的事情。
So this is what we needed to
change about us drop down.
问题是我们把布雷德和他们的每一个都看做了
So here's the issue, we're giving back
Breed and it's sees each one of these and
就好像我不知道这是否会有同样的顺序
is like I don't know if this is
always gonna come in the same order.
所以我就假设它总是不秩序的
So I'm just gonna assume that
it comes always out of order.
我们知道情况不是这样
We know this isn't the case.
如果我们回到使用下拉菜单和状态更新的下拉菜单中，
If we go back to use dropdown that
state dropdown and state update,
状态始终以此顺序返回。
state always comes back in this order.
所以我们其实要比以前更具体，
So we actually have to be more
specific than we were previously,
尽管 useDropdown 以前很快乐
despite the fact that
useDropdown was happy before.
使用的是不快乐的
What's being used is unhappy and
问题并不在于它是否在使用中。
the problem is not there it's
actually in the useDropdown.
所以我们得把它还给它
So here we have to give it back,
这就好像不太会是弦功能
it's like no this is very much
gonna be string FunctionComponent.
它将成为 ReactComponentElement。
It's actually gonna be
a ReactComponentElement.
> > Brian: Nope，是 a， >> Brian:
&gt;&gt; Brian: Nope, it's a,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Let's just go FunctionComponent,
这才是技术上的问题
cuz that's technically what it is.
然后这将成为 SetStateAction。
And then this is gonna
be a SetStateAction.
> > 布莱恩: 这将会是一个字符串。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
this is gonna take in a string.
>> 布莱恩: 让我们去看看这是否解决了我们的问题。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
let's go see if that fixed our problem.
好的
Okay, it did.
所以，让我们先聊一聊这里发生了什么。
So let's go ahead and just chit chat for
a second about what happened here.
这可能是一个非常好的问题
This was actually probably
a really good problem for
因为我觉得我重新写了三次
you to ,because I think I've
rewritten this like three times and
我每次都这样想，我忘记了，我需要这样做。
I run into it every single time that
I forget that I need to do this.
>> 布莱恩: 那么当你给 Typesscript 一个数组，它是一个混合的数组，对，或者
&gt;&gt; Brian: So when you give Typescript an
array, and it's a mixed array, right, or
一个异种阵列
a heterogenous array.
它会假设所有元素都能出现在任何顺序上，对吗 ?
It's going to assume that all the elements
can come in any order, right?
所以我给了它一个字符串，一个元素和一个函数。
So I gave it here a string,
an element, and a function.
我想这可以按任何顺序来找我
I assume that this can come
back to me in any order.
所以我得回去说，不。
So I had to go back and say, nope.
这个，这个，这个，这个，什么都没有，对吧 ?
It's very much this, this, this,
and never anything else, right?
所以现在如果我回到佩特去看看
So now if I go back to
Pet it's gonna look at,
或者不是宠物我们在 SearchParams
or not Pet,
we were in SearchParams rather.
知道这会是个字串我知道
It knows that's gonna be a string,
I know that.
所以没关系的
So it's okay.
这有道理吗
Does that makes sense?
> > 布莱恩: 我们去做个结果吧
&gt;&gt; Brian: So let's go do results.
>> Brian: 将其重命名为 Results.tsx。
&gt;&gt; Brian: Rename this to be Results.tsx.
>> Brian: 因此我们需要从此处抓取 FunctionComponent ，
&gt;&gt; Brian: So we need to grab
FunctionComponent from up here,
FunctionComponent。
FunctionComponent.
我们需要抓住进口动物
And we need to grab Import Animal
从 @frontendmasters/pet ，好吗 ?
from @frontendmasters/pet, okay?
我们会说这需要一个接口
We're gonna say this takes an interface
" IProps " 的 " 宠物: 动物 "
of IProps being pets: Animal array.
然后，此处的结果是带有 IProps的 FunctionComponent 。
And then results here is
a FunctionComponent with IProps.
> > 布莱恩: 我认为是这样。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And I think that's it.
我认为现在的结果应该是快乐的。
I think now results should be happy.
> > 布莱恩: 这些宠物现在是一种动物阵列。
&gt;&gt; Brian: And
those pets is an animal array now.
现在，如果我们回到 SearchParams ，我认为现在应该是快乐的了。
And now if we go back to SearchParams,
I think this should be happy too now.
我的错在哪里
Where's my error?
UpdateBreed 这不开心
UpdateBreed, this wasn't happy.
这有什么问题
What's wrong with this?
向前迈进好吗
New state strings forward, okay.
所以我们一定要回来
So rather than do that,
we're gonna come back here and
说这就是 SetStateAction
say this is actually gonna
be the SetStateAction.
我以为是那样的
I thought that's what that was.
> > Brian: Dispatch ，也许?
&gt;&gt; Brian: Dispatch, maybe?
> > 布莱恩: 我们来试试
&gt;&gt; Brian: Let's try that.
> > 布莱恩: 还有布莱恩: 好的，看起来很开心
&gt;&gt; Brian: And,
&gt;&gt; Brian: Okay, it seems happy with that.
好的。
Okay.
> > 布莱恩: 为了重新说明那里发生的事情，我给出了错误的类型。
&gt;&gt; Brian: So to recap what happened there,
I gave it the wrong type.
后来我在看我是怎么叫 updateBreeds 的
So I was looking at what I was
calling updateBreeds later,
我就像是不明白这是什么对吧
I was like I don't understand
what this is, right?
所以我做了什么我去了
So instead what I did is, I went and
从名为 " Dispatch " 的 " React " 中获取了另一个类型，它很开心。
grabbed a different type from React called
Dispatch, and that one it was happy with.